MARSHA WHALEN

Broussard, LA 70518 (337) 278-4198 marshajune75@gmail.com

Dear Hiring Manager,

As a recent graduate with a Bachelor of Science degree in accounting, and a strong background in the service field, I am seeking a support-oriented remote position. My goal-driven attitude and attention to detail will convey the reasons why, over the past four years, I have been a continuous member of the Dean's List and acquired membership into Phi Theta Kappa Honor Society. My dedication to learning and improvement led to the two-level increase in my professional tax preparer title after my first tax season and has contributed to my consistently high quality assurance scores of 90-100%. With my proven history of exceptional performance, I am excited to share my resume and credentials with you, as I have been anticipating an opportunity to add to my experience, training, and education.

Throughout my time as a tax preparer, student, and support representative, I have portrayed the importance of data accuracy with a strong significance to detail. I have developed strong research capabilities, with the ability to comprehend and apply my findings for effective problem solving. Beyond my accounting degree courses, I have studied a wide range of applicable computer applications, including QuickBooks; Microsoft Office applications, including Project and Access; and Google Sheets and Docs.

With a position within your establishment, I will be able to provide the support necessary for successful project completion, while delivering exceptional service to our clients. I would appreciate the chance to share with you my drive and dedication and as part of your team, I will welcome the opportunity to apply and expand upon my knowledge and skills set.

Thank you for your time and consideration of my credentials. I look forward to hearing from you and discussing this opportunity to become a member of your team.

Sincerely, Marsha Whalen

Enclosure: Resume

marshajune 75@gmail.com

337-278-4198

MARSHA WHALEN

ACCOMPLISHMENT

0

Dean's List all semesters (2017 - 2021)

Microsoft Excel Certification (May 2020)

Waitr Partner Support - Star Agent of the Month (July 2021 & October 2021)

Consistently high scores (90-100%) from Waitr Quality Assurance

SKILLS & ABILITIES

- Proficient in Microsoft Office applications & QuickBooks, Google Docs/Sheets
- Excellent written and verbal business communications
- Detail-oriented, accomplished researcher and problem solver
- Quick learner with experience in multiple computer applications
- Adept at providing personal assistance to clients over the phone or electronically
- Ability to empathize with others and actively listen
- Intermediate knowledge of tax preparation documents and laws for individuals

PROFESSIONAL

TAX ASSOCIATE, SENIOR TAX SPECIALIST, H&R BLOCK, YOUNGSVILLE LA

EXPERIENCE

DECEMBER 2016 - APRIL 2017, DECEMBER 2017 - APRIL 2018

- Prepared tax returns and responsibly increased tax refunds for clients by applying tax deductions and credits, while exercising due diligence and adhering to current tax laws.
- Assisted more experienced tax preparers through research and knowledge application. Increased professional title two levels after first tax season through online coursework and testing.

SUPPORT AGENT, PARTNER SUPPORT AGENT, PREMIER PARTNER SUPPORT REPRESENTATIVE - WAITR, INC / APRIL 2020- PRESENT General Overview:

Trained and worked in customer, restaurant, and driver support positions. By phone and online chats, I assisted with all account and order issues, including escalations and equipment troubleshooting. I also mentored new agents and as Team Lead's Assistant, I assisted other agents and Waitr employees.

More Specialized Tasks:

- Assisting the top revenue-generating restaurants for both OpCos (Waitr and Bite Squad)
- Communicating regularly with Specialized Experience Manager & Retention
 Team
- Auditing and balancing customer refunds and credits
- Responding to escalated restaurant inquiries through HubSpot
- Researching order disputes for restaurants and processing related credits
- Filtering cancellation of service phone calls from restaurants and escalating to Retention Team
- Implementing the premier service strategy as dictated by the leadership team
- Providing administrative support for merchant partners [financials, profile, documentation]
- Researching and escalating payment processing issues to engineering
- Monitoring operational serviceability metrics of restaurant partners to ensure maximum customer exposure
- Monitoring operational performance metrics of restaurant partners to ensure customers are receiving the highest standard of service

• HubSpot CRM software, Slack, Ujet, Kustomer, Zendesk, PandaDoc

EDUCATION

DELGADO COMMUNITY COLLEGE —NEW ORLEANS — MAY 2019

Certificate of Tech Studies – Accounting Office Assistant

DELGADO COMMUNITY COLLEGE —NEW ORLEANS —A.A.S. IN ACCOUNTING — DECEMBER 2019

4.0 GPA, Dean's List all semesters, Phi Theta Kappa Honor Society member

NORTHWESTERN STATE UNIVERSITY – NATCHITOCHES – B.S. IN ACCOUNTING – DECEMBER 2021

3.812 GPA, Dean's List all semesters, QuickBooks, Microsoft Excel Certification, Microsoft Suite, Microsoft Project & Access, Tableau, Canva

References

Casey Martin

Partner Support Manager

Waitr, Inc

caseymmartin17@gmail.com

(337) 274-3069

Kimmie Roberts

Associate Manager of Premier Partner Support

Waitr, Inc

kimmie.roberts@waitrapp.com

(337) 349-4625

Timothy Haaland

Partner Support Team Lead

Waitr, Inc

timothy.haaland@waitrapp.com

(337) 288-0413

Rob Armelin

Partner Support Team Lead

Waitr, Inc

robert.armelin@waitrapp.com

(337) 563-1689

March 28, 2022

To whom it may concern,

I have been working with Marsha Whalen for quite some time now, not as her direct supervisor until recently. She applied for the position on my team and was chosen based on her past performance as one of our normal Partner Support agents. She has an excellent work ethic, making sure to do her work quickly and efficiently. She is always willing to help others in need when she can. Has a great attitude and attention to detail. She was brought on at a difficult time for our department but through it all she made the best of it. Even with limited training she jumped in and started working hard figuring things out and excelling. She would make a wonderful addition to any team as she will always give 100% effort with her can-do attitude and apply herself to the best of her ability. I am very grateful for her contributions over the years to this company and the partner support department. I am very

confident that she has not only the worth ethic but the intelligence, and communication skills to add value to whatever company or position she works.

Best Regards,

Kimmie Roberts

Associate Manager

(337)349-4625

kimmie.roberts@waitrapp.com